Prefabs in Unity are preconfigured game objects
Unity におけるプレハブは事前設定されたゲームオブジェクトであり、
that you create in the scene
シーンで作成して、
and store in the project.
プロジェクトに格納します。
They can then be instantiated or cloned,
これらはインスタンス化（クローン化）できます。
meaning to create an instance of them
すなわち、ゲーム中にインスタンスの作成が
during the game.
出来ます。
They have all manner of uses and are a key part
あらゆる用途で使用することが出来て、
of development in Unity.
Unity 開発における重要な部分です。
They are used for everything from rockets
ロケット、敵、プロシージャルなレベルまで、
to enemies, to procedural levels.
あらゆることに使用されます。
To make a prefab simply create your game object
プレハブを作成するには、ゲームオブジェウトを
in it's desired configuration in your scene,
希望するとおりの設定でシーン上に作成します。
from whatever components you need,
希望するコンポーネントから構成したうえで
and then drag it to the project panel
プロジェクトパネルにドラッグして、
to save it as a prefab.
プレハブとして保存します。
It can then be deleted from the scene.
その後はシーンから削除してかまいません。
To edit a prefab you can either select it in the project,
プレハブを編集するには、プロジェクトで選択して、
and adjust properties in the inspector.
インスペクタ上でプロパティを調整します。
Or drag an instance of it back in to the scene,
もうひとつの方法としては、インスタンスをシーン上にドラッグして、
edit it in the inspector,
インスペクタ上で編集して
and then press the apply button at the top.
上部にある Apply ボタンを押下します。
This saves changes back in to the prefab
これにより変更が逆にプレハブに反映されます。
and you can then remove the instance from the scene
そして、その後は再びインスタンスをシーンから
yet again.
破棄して問題ありません。
Also, if you have many instances of a prefab,
さらに、プレハブのインスタンスがたくさんある場合に、
and you make edits to one of them,
ひとつだけ編集を行って、
and decide you would like others to be the same
他も同様にしたい場合は
you can hit apply.
Apply を入力するだけです。
The other instances will inherit this update
他のインスタンスはこの変更内容を
from the prefab's settings.
プレハブの設定から継承します。
Likewise if you make a change to
同様にして、
one of your instances
インスタンスのひとつに変更を加えて、
and you decide you don't like it anymore
その変更をやっぱり取りやめたい場合、
you can revert to the settings of the prefab
プレハブの設定に元に戻すには
by clicking the revert button at the top.
上部にある Revert ボタンをクリックします。 (翻訳:gamesonytablet)